We in this—, ro- ro—
Rockin' with, rockin' with Patrick
Told shawty, "Just go ahead and put in that work" Put in that work, put it
She throw it back for a young nigga, she like to twerk Oh, oh
She talk too much, lil' bitch, I don't like to flirt Say what?, What? What? What?
I'm a bad bitch too, lil' bitch, we both go skirts Bitch, me too
I feel all these hits up in my soul Say what?
Make all my brothers rich, that's my goal That's my goal
No, I can never switch on my bros
Had to fuck on your bitch, on the low Say what? Mm- mm, ha, ha
Sing to me, baby, just sing to me, baby, yeah
Too many flows, too many flows, like the '80s, hold up Mm- mm; Too many flows, say what?
Too many flows, my flow crack like the '80s, ayy I bet ya
I got the dough, I'm finna push it on your face I got the do–, on God
Too many hoes, tryna come suck me all day And what? Say what?
They movin' slow, told these niggas, better up they pace Ayy
You a lil' ho, run in your crib, give a fuck 'bout your place You a lil' ho, okay, okay
Told shawty, "Just go ahead and put in that work" Put in that work, put it
She throw it back for a young nigga, she like to twerk Oh, oh
She talk too much, lil' bitch, I don't like to flirt Say what?, What? What? What?
I'm a bad bitch too, lil' bitch, we both go skirts Bitch, me too
These nig gas im post er, S L C Punk Ha
My bul lets just like wa ter, pus sy -ass nig ga get dunked Boop- boop- boop- boop
I'm woke, I might just skimp my head, shawty, I feel like a monk Say what?
And shawty just got some plays for me, I kick the lil' shit like Gronk Let's go, let's go
Kick the lil' shit like Gronk, throw me a play like Brady Let's go, okay
Fuckin' that bitch every day, fuckin' that bitch on the daily Say what? What?
Niggas be pussy, okay, stick in his face, we gon' raid it
And I don't give a fuck 'bout your bae, we gon' fuck around and take We in this—, ro- ro—
They don't know what I been on lately, so I show these niggas, I ain't playin' Rockin' with, rockin' with Patrick
Bad bitch wanna fuck, she faceless
You got sticks in your Wraith? I'll take it Wraith
Kill your ass and leave your ass in a lake, that bitch tryna fuck first date Yee, yee
Fuck a bitch, I'm gettin' that pape', like Drake, got my bitch jaded Say what? What?
Okay
Bitch, drink my nut, get faded
You don't know, so you get hit Get hit
Burst in, when I came, got lit
Burst in when his shit got raided
You a hatin' ass nigga and I hate it
Lil' Nine, know I need my cake